# ERICK AZEN

Electronic Engineer formed in the U.K., Six Sigma Black Belt with over 16 years of work experience and an entrepreneurial spirit with drive for results. Experience in the areas of software development, R&D, manufacturing, sales, project management, finance, procurement and supply chain ranging from leading international engineering teams to double digit million P&L management. Multi-cultural, having worked in three different countries with accumulated experience in several management training programs including an Executive MBA at the Kellogg School of Management.

## **Personal**

- Married, 1 son
- Brazilian and German nationalities
- Fluent in Portuguese, English and German, intermediate Spanish and basic French



# **Experience**

#### 2014 - 2020 Restaurant Brands International

- Vice-President Head of Global Procurement (Zug, Switzerland)
- Senior Director Global Indirect Procurement (Miami, USA)
- Director Global Business Development (Miami, USA)
- Director Development and Supply Chain (Munich, Germany)

#### 2004 - 2014 Knorr-Bremse Systeme für Nutzfahrzeuge

- Aftermarket Product Portfolio Team Lead Europe (Munich, Germany)
- Program Manager & Technical Sales (Munich, Germany)
- Management Trainee (Germany)

## 2001 - 2002 Siemens AG

• Application Software Developer for Telecommunications (Germany)

Education	
2015 - 2017	Kellogg School of Management Executive MBA (Miami, USA)
2012	<u>University of St. Gallen</u> Foundations of Management MBA Course (St. Gallen, Switzerland)
1998 - 2004	<u>University of Surrey</u> Masters in Electronic Engineering (Honors Degree with Merit – UK)